docdroid.net 2019-12-31

# Privacy | DocDroid

DocDroid is maintained by Lunaweb GmbH, Munich (Germany). As a Data Controller, DocDroid is bound by the requirements of the General Data Protection Regulations (GDPR). If you do not agree to our Privacy Policy and the other terms stated below, please do not use our services and [let us know about your concerns](https://www.docdroid.net/contact). We reserve the right to change our Privacy Policy and other terms stated below at any time. 

##  Personal Data Collected by Us 

By visiting our website and/or using our API, your IP address will be logged along with the HTTP referrer, user agent and the dates of access (log data). 

If you decide to create a DocDroid account, we collect your eMail address, your chosen username, your name and your profile picture. 

If you decide to subscribe, we need to additionally collect your full name, physical address, company name and VAT id. We do not collect your credit card data. All financial transactions are handled through our payment provider [Stripe](https://www.stripe.com/). 

##  Handling of Your Uploaded Documents 

In the course of providing the service your files are transferred to and from servers of DocDroid. We do not read, look into or mine any data from your files or its metadata. We do not make any copies of it. All file processing is done by machine and there is no human interaction with your files. Your files are deleted irreversible from our servers when you click the Delete button. 

##  Use of Your Personal Data 

We do log your IP address to prevent abuse of our service and for broad demographic analysis. We do not link this information to any personally identifiable information. If you provide an eMail address we use it to communicate with you. 

If you buy a package or subscribe for our services your name, company and address is used to create the invoice and for prevention of fraud. Your VAT id may be used to check if you qualify to exempt of paying VAT. 

## Sharing Your Data

We will not, under any circumstances whatsoever, give out or sell your documents or personal data to anyone. Also, no one, you did not provide the DocDroid link, will ever have access to your documents. 

If you subscribe, we need to send your name and your address to our payment provider [Stripe](https://www.stripe.com/), which is based outside the European Union. This is necessary to process your payment. 

If use any contact form (support, abuse report) or if you mail us, we send your name, email address and message to our ticket system [Freshdesk](https://freshdesk.com/). Freshdesk is based outside the European Union. 

## Keeping your Data

We will keep your personal data for as long as it is necessary to provide you with our services. Your documents are deleted irreversible from our servers within 7 days when use the "Delete" button. Documents are deleted automatically after 60 days without view (Does not apply to Pro accounts). 

If you delete your account, all personal data and all your documents will be permanently deleted within 7 days. All log data (IP address, user agent, referrer) is deleted after 14 days. 

## Your Rights

Your data can be modified in the Settings menu. Also, you can delete your account there. This will delete your account and all associated data within 7 days. This also deletes all data on payment provider Stripe and ticket system Freshdesk (if there is any). 

You can modify and delete your documents [on your own](https://www.docdroid.net/mydocuments). If you have forget your account credentials or if you didn't create an account, you can [contact us](https://www.docdroid.net/contact) and we will do it for you. 

## Security

We are committed to protect your personal data and your files. All transfers from and to DocDroid are SSL encrypted. All DocDroid servers are located in the European Union, are protected and cannot be accessed by third parties. 

## Cookies

DocDroid stores so-called "cookies" in order to be able to offer you a comprehensive range of functions and to make it easier to use our websites. "Cookies" are small files which are stored on your computer with the help of the internet browser. If you do not want to use "cookies", you can prevent "cookies" from being stored on your computer using the corresponding settings on your internet browser. Please note that this may restrict the functional capability and the range of functions of our offer. 

## Analytics

We use Google Analytics to store information about how visitors use our website so that we may make improvements and give visitors a better user experience. Google Analytics is a third-party information storage system by Google that records information about the pages you visit, the length of time you were on specific pages and the website in general, how you arrived at the site and what you clicked on. You can [opt out](http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout) of the usage of Google Analytics on this and all other websites using a browser plugin.
